So in here, let's make a quick readme.md.
现在，让我们来快速创建一个 "README.md" 文件
Just so we can talk about what we're going to be making here.
这样我们就可以讨论一下接下来我们要处理的内容
So in this section, we're gonna be using raw HTML slash JavaScript
在这一节中，我们将先使用原始的 "HTML / JavaScript"
in conjunction with our smart contracts to build this website.
结合我们的智能合约来构建这个网站
Later on. We will use next Jas slash react,
接下来，我们要使用一种更加现代化的技术栈
which is a more modern stack to build our websites here.
"Nextjs / Reactjs" 来构建我们的网站
But learning understanding how to do everything with HTML and JavaScript first,
但首先来学习和理解如何使用 HTML 和 JavaScript 来完成所有的操作
is going to make our lives a lot easier come later on down the road.
会让我们之后的学习工作变得更轻松一些
But as we know, all websites use HTML as kind of their scaffolding for what they look like.
但正如我们所知的，所有网站都使用 HTML 作为它们的骨架来支撑外观
So let's go ahead and create our HTML for our website,
所以让我们继续，来为我们的网站创建一个 HTML 文件
we'll call it index dot HTML.
我们把它命名为 "index.html"
And this is going to be the basic scaffolding or the basic bones of what our website is going to look like.
这将是我们网站的基本骨架，它决定了网站的基本结构和外观
Now, in VS code, if you go ahead and just type exclamation mark index dot HTML,
现在到 VS Code 中，如果你在 "index.html" 中输入一个感叹号("!")
and you click the first thing that pops up,
然后点击弹出来的第一项
it'll automatically populate your code your file here with some basic HTML setup.
它就会自动在你的代码文件中填充一些基本的 HTML 设置
If it doesn't do this for you,
如果它并不适合你
feel free to copy paste the basic setup from the GitHub repository associated with this course,
那么你可以复制粘贴课程关联的 GitHub 仓库中的基本设置
we have our doctype. HTML,
我们有 ``
we have some HTML tags telling us that everything in between here is going to be an HTML,
还有一些 HTML 标签，告诉我们这里的所有内容都是 HTML
which is great.
非常好
However, for simplicity, we don't need most of this.
然而，为了简单起见，我们并不需要其中的大多数内容
So we're going to make this a little bit easier.
所以我们要让它变得更简单一些
We're going to delete this line, this line and this line.
我们要删除这一行，这一行，还有这一行
And we're just going to change the title to fund me app.
然后直接把标题改成 "Fund Me App"
And then inside of our body, we can do something like or Hello.
接着在 `` 内部，我们可以输入，比如说 `Hello!`
And now we have the bare bones to create a website just with this.
现在我们就有了创建网站的基本骨架了，就是现在这些
Now to show this on a website, we can do one of two things.
现在，要想把它展示到网站上，我们有两种方法可以选择
If you are using Visual Studio code,
如果你使用的是 Visual Studio Code
I'm going to recommend you install the extension live server. And it looks like this.
那么我建议你安装扩展 "live server"，就是这个
And I'll have the extension ID for this extension in the GitHub repository associated with this course,
我会把这个扩展的 ID 放到课程关联的 GitHub 仓库中
this is going to allow us to easily spin up an HTML website.
它可以让我们非常轻松的打开一个 HTML 网站
So we'll go ahead and install this.
所以我们继续，把它安装上
And if you're not using Visual Studio Code,
如果你不使用 Visual Studio Code
I'll show you a different way in just a second.
那么我稍后会向你展示一种不同的方式
Once this is installed, you should have this little go live button at the bottom.
把这个安装好以后，你在底部就应该会有这么一个小的 "Go Live" 按钮
And if you don't, you can always open up your command palette,
如果没有的话，你总可以通过打开你的命令面板
which again, you can open up by hitting View command palette,
再次提醒，你可以通过点击查看("View")来打开命令面板("Command Palette")
and you can type in live server
然后你可以输入 "live server"
and just say open with live server
然后选择 "Open with Live Server"
but we're going to just click this go live button.
但我们这里就直接点击这个 "Go Live" 按钮了
And it's going to say starting
然后它就会显示 "Starting"
and it's actually going to open up your browser with our index dot HTML.
接着它就会打开你的浏览器，使用的就是我们的 "index.html"
We can actually see our website is being called Save on 120 7.0 point 0.1.
我们可以看到，我们的网站托管在了 "127.0.0.1"
This is known as the loopback, or local host endpoint, we're on port 5501.
这就是所谓的“回环”("loopback")或者说本地主机端点("local host endpoint")，我们位于端口 5501
If you're not familiar with the ports, don't worry about that for now,
如果对端口("port")并不熟悉，暂时也不用担心
we have our index dot HTML here.
总之我们这里已经有了我们的 "index.html" 了
And if we change this to something like what's good, we hit save.
如果我们将其更改为，比如说 "Whats good?"，点击保存
If it doesn't automatically refresh, we'd come over here and refresh.
如果它没有自动刷新，我们可以到这边来刷新一下
And we'd see that being reflected here.
并且我们可以看到它已经反映在这里了
If you've never created a website before, you've essentially just done it, congratulations,
如果你以前从来没创建过网站的话，那么你现在已经基本上做到了，恭喜你
you might get this.vs code folder.
你可能会获得这么一个 ".vscode" 文件夹
a.vs code folder allows you to make settings specifically for the repo that you're working with,
这个 ".vscode" 文件夹允许你对正在使用的代码库进行专门的设置
for your code editor for VS code,
它适用于 VS Code 代码编辑器
but we're going to mostly ignore it for now.
但我们现在暂时会忽略掉它
Now, if you're not using Visual Studio Code,
现在，如果你使用的不是 Visual Studio Code
what you can do is you can just run this in the browser.
那么你可以直接在浏览器中运行这个文件
So one thing you could do is you could right click it, and I'm using a Mac. So I'm going to hit Reveal in Finder,
你可以右键点击它，我用的是 Mac，所以我选择的是“在 Finder 中显示”
aka reveal where it's located.
也就是显示它在本地的位置
And you can just double click it, and boom, now it's running right in your browser.
接着，你可以直接双击打开它，嘭，它已经在你的浏览器中运行了
Instead of pointing to your localhost, it's going to be pointing directly to your local file path.
只不过不是指向你的本地主机，而是直接指向你的本地文件路径
Now one final version that we could do
这里还有一个最终方案可以使用
that I'm going to highly recommend you don't do.
但我强烈推荐你不要这么做
But it's another option,
不过这也是一种选择
we're actually going to download a package for you using no Jas, which allows us to serve up HTTP.
我们要为你的 node.js 下载一个包，这个包允许你使用 HTTP 服务
And we're gonna install it the exact same way we've installed our other packages,
安装它的方法就和安装其它包完全一样
we can do yarn, add dash dash dev HTTP hyphen server.
我们要执行 `yarn add --dev http-server`
And you may still want to add it anyways.
你可能仍然想要添加它
But now, we'll get some node modules for this HTTP server package,
但是现在，我们要获取一些用于这个 "http-server" 的 node 模块。
we'll get a package json, and of course, a yarn dot lock as well.
我们获得了 "package.json"，当然了，还有 "yarn.lock"
And what we can do is we can stop this down here, stop that live server.
我们先中断这里的 "Live Server"
And if we go back to our website, refresh, it'll now be blank.
回到我们的网站，刷新，它现在是空的了
And we can run yarn HTTP server.
然后我们运行 `yarn http-server`
And this will do the exact same thing.
它做的就是完全相同的事
And we get, and if we come over, and we refresh, we'll see what's good.
如果我们转到这边，刷新一下，就会看到 "Whats good?"
Now this one is a little bit more finicky.
这个有点麻烦的是
And after you make a change, like, Hey, what's good,
当你做了一些修改后，比如说 "Hey whats good?"
you might have to close it, and then reopen it and then refresh.
你可能需要先关掉它，然后重新打开，然后再刷新
So I do recommend that if you're on Visual Studio code, you definitely just use this little go live button,
所以我建议，如果你用的是 Visual Studio Code，那么你可以直接使用这个小的 "Go Live" 按钮
because it'll reflect your changes a lot nicer.
因为它可以更好地反映你的更改
So let's go ahead and hit the Go Live button. Hey, what's good pops up.
所以我们继续，点击 "Go Live" 按钮，"Hey whats good" 弹了出来
Okay, cool. Our HTML is working perfectly.
OK，酷~ 我们的 HTML 正在完美运行